let's have a look at converting color to
让我们来看看如何将颜色转换为
grayscale and the challenges you may
灰度和您可能面临的挑战
encounter here I have used three very
在这里相遇我用了三个很
different colors that are easily
不同的颜色很容易
distinguished
显赫
let's see how they look like in
让我们看看它们是什么样子的
grayscale I go to filters color
灰度我转到滤镜颜色
grayscale I click on live preview
灰度级我点击实时预览
we see in grayscale they now look
我们看到他们现在看起来是灰阶的
exactly the same
一模一样
so how do we solve this problem
那么，我们如何解决这个问题呢？
I will remove the grayscale effect by
我将通过以下方式消除灰度效果
going to filters remove filters
转到滤镜删除滤镜
let's try again I go to filters color
让我们再试一次，我转到滤镜颜色
grayscale let's say I want blue to be
比方说，我想让蓝色成为
the darkest color
最暗的颜色
to do this I will decrease the lightness
要做到这一点，我将降低亮度
of blue
蓝色的
and I want red to be in between blue and
我想要红色在蓝色和蓝色之间
green
绿色
I want to further increase the contrast
我想进一步增加对比度
between the colors
在颜色之间
I increase lightness and I make blue and
我增加了亮度，我做了蓝色和
red darker
较深的红色
I click on apply and on close
我点击Apply，然后点击Close
this is what I would expect these colors
这就是我所期待的这些颜色
to look like in grayscale
看起来像是灰色的
I need a black and white variant of my
我需要一个黑白版本的我的
logo
徽标
but applying the grayscale filter will
但应用灰度滤镜将
not actually change the colors
并不是真的改变颜色
this is because a filter is like a live
这是因为过滤器就像是带电的
path effect the path effect changes a
路径效果路径效果更改为
path but the original path still exists
路径，但原始路径仍然存在
and this is also true for a filter the
筛选器也是如此，
grayscale filter only changes the
灰度滤镜仅更改
appearance of the colors
颜色的外观
the filter will be applied when I export
导出时将应用该筛选器
a PNG
阿巴新
but if I want to send someone a true
但如果我想给某人发送一个真实的
grayscale SVG I will have to change the
灰度SVG I将不得不更改
actual colors for this video I gave the
这个视频的实际颜色我给了
paths their corresponding color
路径及其对应的颜色
to quickly see what colors you used in
快速查看您使用的是什么颜色
your document Open document resources
您的文档打开文档资源
I see I used five colors
我知道我用了五种颜色
I can not only see what colors I used
我不仅可以看到我用的是什么颜色
but also which fonts
还包括哪些字体
now let's convert the colors to
现在让我们将颜色转换为
grayscale
灰度级
I will drag fill and stroke to the tabs
我会将填充和描边拖到选项卡上
below
在下面
I click on Steam middle
我点击Steam Medium
I drag saturation to zero
我把饱和度拉到零
If a color is used in more paths I right
如果在更多的路径中使用一种颜色，我是对的
click and choose select same fill color
单击并选择选择相同的填充颜色
then I drag saturation to zero
然后我将饱和度拖到零
I do this for all five colors
我对所有五种颜色都这样做
now let's say I want the cup to be
现在假设我希望杯子是
completely black
完全黑色
to do this I drag lightness to zero
为此，我将亮度拖到零